[Music]
[Música]
Let's wait before moving on to the next
esperemos antes de pasar al siguiente
topic. I'd like to react with you
tema Me gustaría reaccionar contigo
to a bombshell that our
a un bombazo que acaba de soltar nuestra
colleague Ave Nocturne just dropped, which interests us all,
compañera ave nocturna que a todos nos
because the first part of this
interesa porque la primera parte de esta
bombshell was
bomba la dio precisamente
delivered precisely by Marina here. Who
la dio precisamente Marina aquí Que la
brought it by the
trajo por la trajo por mano de
hand of José Alcaide, I don't know if you
de mano de José alcaide no sé si lo
know him, who is a wonderful friend of the
conoce que es un maravilloso amigo del
Canal
Canal
Cierre. In reference to the Golden Nail
cierre En referencia al Golden nail
Congress, I have pronounced it. The
congreso lo he pronunciado El Congreso
Nail Congress by José Alcaide, which he is organizing
de las uñas de José alcaide que organiza
in Madrid in June
en Madrid en junio
2023, in Madrid, we have a new bombshell,
este 2023 en Madrid tenemos nueva bomba
let's go see it, let's go see it.
vamos a verlo vamos a verlo
[Music] I
[Música]
have an idea.
tengo una idea
Look, María Jesús Ruiz, my goodness. [Music
Mira María Jesús Ruiz madre mía
] [
[Música]
Hey, it made you feel uneasy to be here, eh, you have
Oye pues te desaseó estar aquí eh tenés
gossip, she will be here broadcasting
salseo estará por aquí retransmitiendo
this, eh, Gloria Camila, yes. And they are
esto eh Gloria Camila sí Y son unas
very successful guests because they always
invitadas muy acertadas porque siempre
attract a lot of media. Look, there
atraen mucho a los medios mira ahí
you have Ivonne Reyes, who is now
tienes tú a Ivonne reyes que ahora está
in the story that she lost the trial
en la historia de que perdió el juicio
with Pepe as an agent, she is going to ask her
con Pepe de agente le va a preguntar que
how she is, like Alejandro, her son, who is
cómo está como Alejandro su hijo que es
great.  They're also going to
estupendo también también le van a
ask her what she thinks about all the latest developments.
preguntar qué piensa de todo lo último
Then you have Gloria Camila who's
luego tienes a Gloria Camila que está
doing a few outings and she's always
haciendo poquitas salidas y siempre
super interesting because she can
súper interesante porque puede hablar
also talk about survivors, she can tell us
también de supervivientes puede contar
how her father is, the museum, everything. And then
cómo está su padre el museo todo y luego
María Jesús Ruiz, who is a person who
María Jesús Ruiz que es una persona que
also has a boyfriend today, who has had
también hoy el novio que ha tenido toda
this whole angina story, everything they
esta historia de la angina de pecho todo
say about her, the father of her
lo que dicen de ella el padre de su hija
oldest daughter who is also in bad shape. The truth
mayor que está fatal también la verdad
is that she's very, very well chosen. Yes,
es que está muy muy bien escogidas eh Sí
yes, yes, we'll
sí sí
be there, we'll be there. I don't know if I'll go
estaremos ahí estaremos no sé si Iré yo
personally, maybe I will, but what will
personalmente puede que sí pero lo que
be there is teles to the CEO 100%
estará allí teles al ceo 100%
[Music]
[Música]